A Guide to the Social Movements Collection 1941-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Save the Children Foundation n.d. (Box-folder 10:25)
- Scholarship, Education, and Defense Fund for Racial Equality (SEDFRE) 1969-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 10:26)
- Science for Vietnam 1971, n.d. (Box-folder 10:27)
- Scientific American 1964-1969 (Box-folder 10:28)
- Scientists' Institute for Public Information n.d. (Box-folder 10:29)
- Scott Camil Defense Committee 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 10:30)
- Scott for Senate Committee 1972 (Box-folder 10:31)
- Seacoast Area Workers Committee 1972 (Box-folder 10:32)
- Selective Service System 1970 (Box-folder 10:33)
- Selma Project 1965-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 10:34)
- Set the Date Now 1972 (Box-folder 10:35)
- Shanti Nonviolent Action Center n.d. (Box-folder 10:36)
- Sheldon Day Care Center 1970 (Box-folder 10:37)
- Shell Strike Support Committee n.d. (Box-folder 10:38)
- Shoshana (Pat Swinton) Defense Committee 1975 (Box-folder 10:39)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation n.d. (Box-folder 10:40)
- Simon Fraser University 1970 (Box-folder 10:41)
- Sisters Stand n.d. (Box-folder 10:42)
- Situationist International n.d. (Box-folder 10:43)
- Social Responsibilities Roundtable 1979 (Box-folder 10:44)
- Social-Revolutionary Anarchist Federation 1972-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 10:45)
- Social Service Employees Union n.d. (Box-folder 10:46)
- Socialist Labor Party 1969, n.d. (Box-folder 10:47)
- Socialist Labor Party of Canada 1974 (Box-folder 10:48)
- Socialist Revolution Collective 1970 (Box-folder 11:1)
- Socialist Workers National Campaign Committee 1968-1972 (Box-folder 11:2)
- Socialist Workers Party 1968-1980 (Box-folder 11:3)
- Society for Humane Abortion 1964-1971, n.d. (Box-folder 11:4)
- Society for Individual Liberty n.d. (Box-folder 11:5)
- Society for the Prevention of World War III 1968 (Box-folder 11:6)
- The Society of African Culture 1974 (Box-folder 11:7)
- Society of Brothers 1967-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 11:8)
- Soldiers of the Cross 1972 (Box-folder 11:9)
- Soledad Brothers Legal Committee n.d. (Box-folder 11:10)
- Solidarity Book Store 1973, n.d. (Box-folder 11:11)
- The Solidarity Committee for Support of Arab Liberation Movements 1973, n.d. (Box-folder 11:12)
- Solidarity Committee with the Argentine People 1976 (Box-folder 11:13)
- Some Hard to Locate Sources of Information 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11:14)
- South Baltimore General Hospital Workers Committee 1973 (Box-folder 11:15)
- South Carolina Voter Education Project 1969 (Box-folder 11:16)
- South Florida Peace Coalition n.d. (Box-folder 11:17)
- South of Tuk 1974 (Box-folder 11:18)
- South Vietnam National Front for Liberation-Information Commission n.d. (Box-folder 11:19)
- Southern Conference Educational Fund (The Southern Patriot) 1970-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 11:20)
- Southern Highlands Literary Fund, Inc. n.d. (Box-folder 11:21)
- Southern Regional Council, Inc. 1959-1964 (Box-folder 11:22)
- Southern Regional Council, Inc. 1965-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 11:23)
- Southern Regional Spartacist Leagues n.d. (Box-folder 11:24)
- Southern Students Human Rights Project n.d. (Box-folder 11:25)
- Southwest Research and Information Center n.d. (Box-folder 11:26)
- Student Non-violent Coordinating Committee 1966 (Box-folder 11:27)
- Students for a Democratic Society n.d. (Box-folder 11:28)
- Support-in-Action n.d. (Box-folder 11:29)
- Susan Saxe Defense Committee 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11:30)
- Tactics 1970 (Box-folder 11:31)
- Take One 1972 (Box-folder 11:32)
- Times Change Press 1970-1973 (Box-folder 11:33)
- Today's Comix n.d. (Box-folder 12:1)
- Toronto American Exiles Association n.d. (Box-folder 12:2)
- Toronto Anti-Draft Programme n.d. (Box-folder 12:3)
- John Tower 1969 (Box-folder 12:4)
- Transaction 1969 (Box-folder 12:5)
- The Trumpet 1969 (Box-folder 12:6)
- Truth Crusader-Inside Information 1972 (Box-folder 12:7)
- Turn Toward Peace [1974] (Box-folder 12:8)
- Tusculum College 1968 (Box-folder 12:9)
- Twin Cities Draft Information Center 1970 (Box-folder 12:10)
- Twin Oaks Community, Virginia 1970 (Box-folder 12:11)
- Tzedek Tzedek 1975, n.d. (Box-folder 12:12)
- Union of Concerned Scientists 1975-1980 (Box-folder 12:13)
- Unitarian Universalist Association 1965-1971 (Box-folder 12:14)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America)-Women's Department 1977 (Box-folder 12:15)
- United Church of Christ 1960-1971 (Box-folder 12:16)
- United Co-operative Industries n.d. (Box-folder 12:17)
- United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America [1970] (Box-folder 12:18)
- United Methodist Voluntary service for COs n.d. (Box-folder 12:19)
- United States Commission on Civil Rights 1965-1971 (Box-folder 12:20)
- United States Committee Against Militarization 1968-1969 (Box-folder 12:21)
- United States Congress 1965-1974 (Box-folder 12:22)
- United States Directory Service 1971 (Box-folder 12:23)
- United States National Student Association 1963-1964 (Box-folder 12:24)
- United States National Student Association 1965-1972, n.d. (Box-folder 12:25)
- U.S. News and World Report 1967 (Box-folder 13:1)
- United States People's Fund for the United Nations, Inc. n.d. (Box-folder 13:2)
- United States Servicemen's Fund [1971] (Box-folder 13:3)
- United States Student Press Association 1966 (Box-folder 13:4)
- University Christian Movement 1967-1969, n.d. (Box-folder 13:5)
- University of Buffalo 1961 (Box-folder 13:6)
- University of Maryland, College Park 1967-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 13:7)
- University of Mississippi-Rebel Underground 1962-1963 (Box-folder 13:8)
- University of Virginia 1968 (Box-folder 13:9)
- University of Virginia-Alderman Library 1970 (Box-folder 13:10)
- University of Virginia-The Virginia Patriot 1966 (Box-folder 13:11)
- Russel R. Veh 1971 (Box-folder 13:12)
- Vietnam 1965-1971, n.d. (Box-folder 13:13)
- Vietnam: Challenge to Conscience n.d. (Box-folder 13:14)
- Vietnam Education Project 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13:15)
- Vietnam Gift Pac n.d. (Box-folder 13:16)
- Vietnam Moratorium Committee 1969-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 13:17)
- Vietnam Work-In n.d. (Box-folder 13:18)
- The Vineyard: The National Independent Orthodox Journal 1973-1974 (Box-folder 13:19)
- Virginia Citizens Consumer Council n.d. (Box-folder 13:20)
- Virginia Citizens for Peace in Vietnam n.d. (Box-folder 13:21)
- Virginia Commission on the Status of Women 1974 (Box-folder 13:22)
- Virginia 1968 (Box-folder 13:23)
- Virginia Commonwealth University 1969 (Box-folder 13:24)
- Virginia Community Development Organization n.d. (Box-folder 13:25)
- Virginia Council on Human Relations 1964-1970, n.d. (Box-folder 13:26)
- Virginia ERA Central 1974-1976 (Box-folder 13:27)
- Virginia Equal Rights Amendment Ratification Council 1974 (Box-folder 13:28)
- Virginia Improved Environment Week 1970 (Box-folder 13:29)
- Virginia League for Planned Parenthood 1971 (Box-folder 13:30)
- Virginia Libertarian Party 1974 (Box-folder 13:31)
- Virginia Record 1967 (Box-folder 13:32)
- Virginia Solar Energy Association 1980 (Box-folder 13:33)
- Virginia State AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education 1964 (Box-folder 13:34)
- Virginia Students Civil Rights Committee 1966-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 13:35)
- Virginia Welfare Rights Organization [1971] (Box-folder 13:36)
- Vocations for Social Change 1968-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 13:37)
- War Control Planners, Inc. 1969 (Box-folder 13:38)
- War Resisters League: fliers and mailings 1965-1975, n.d. (Box-folder 14:1)
- War Resisters League: letters and newsletters 1966-1976 (Box-folder 14:2)
- War Resisters League: pamphlets and booklets 1960-1976, n.d. (Box-folder 14:3)
- Washington Office on Latin America 1979 (Box-folder 14:4)
- Washington Peace Center 1972-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 14:5)
- Washington Summer Action 1965, n.d (Box-folder 14:6)
- Washington Watch 1972-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 14:7)
- Wednesdays in Washington 1966 (Box-folder 14:8)
- Weekly Action Project n.d. (Box-folder 14:9)
- Weekly Guardian Associates n.d. (Box-folder 14:10)
- The Welcome Thieu Committee n.d. (Box-folder 14:11)
- Western Michigan University-The Western Activist n.d. (Box-folder 14:12)
- Westminster Presbyterian Church-Charlottesville, Virginia 1967, n.d. (Box-folder 14:13)
- Whack! 1971 (Box-folder 14:14)
- The Whale's Tale n.d. (Box-folder 14:15)
- White Christian Intelligence Network 1970-1971, n.d. (Box-folder 14:16)
- White Legion Books 1973 (Box-folder 14:17)
- Wichita Workers and Oppressed Peoples United 1975 (Box-folder 14:18)
- Laird Wilcox 1969 (Box-folder 14:19)
- Wildcat 1971, n.d. (Box-folder 14:20)
- The Wilderness Society n.d. (Box-folder 14:21)
- The Wilfred Burchett Fund 1975 (Box-folder 14:22)
- Wisconsin Alliance n.d. (Box-folder 14:23)
- Wisconsin Draft Resistance Union n.d. (Box-folder 14:24)
- Women for Disarmament 1974 (Box-folder 14:25)
- Women Against Daddy Warbucks n.d. (Box-folder 14:26)
- Women for the Conference for Women and Health 1973 (Box-folder 14:27)
- Women Strike for Peace 1979 (Box-folder 14:28)
- Women's History Research Center Library 1971-1974, n.d. (Box-folder 14:29)
- Worker's Defense League 1969 (Box-folder 14:30)
- Worker's Fight 1973 (Box-folder 14:31)
- Workers Viewpoint 1975 (Box-folder 14:32)
- World Conference on Religion and Peace 1970 (Box-folder 14:33)
- World Council of Churches 1970-1973 (Box-folder 14:34)
- World Federalist Youth n.d. (Box-folder 14:35)
- World Fellowship, Inc. 1970 (Box-folder 14:36)
- World Future Society n.d. (Box-folder 14:37)
- World Peace Council 1973 (Box-folder 15:1)
- World Peace Study Mission 1963-1964 (Box-folder 15:2)
- World Rehabilitation Fund, Inc. 1974 (Box-folder 15:3)
- World Union of National Socialists 1972 (Box-folder 15:4)
- Wounded Knee Legal Defense/Offense Committee 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 15:5)
- Wycliffe Bible Translator 1974 (Box-folder 15:6)
- The Yellow Dragon Coop of Charlottesville n.d. (Box-folder 15:7)
- Young Americans for Freedom 1968-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 15:8)
- Youth Against War and Fascism 1971-1973, n.d. (Box-folder 15:9)
- Young Lords Party n.d. (Box-folder 15:10)
- Young Workers Liberation League 1974, n.d. (Box-folder 15:11)
- Youth for Goldwater 1964 (Box-folder 15:12)
- Youth Liberation 1979, n.d. (Box-folder 15:13)
- Youth Resources Inc. n.d. (Box-folder 15:14)
- Youth International Party News Service n.d. (Box-folder 15:15)